Contact

404 6163466 (Work) naphtali_edge@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/taliedge-3b18654b (LinkedIn) www.edgeconsultingcompany.com (Personal)

Top Skills

Fellow American College of Healthcare Executives Certified Executive Nursing Practice Nurse Executive Advanced--Board Certified

Honors-Awards

Case in Point Platinum Award Best Transition of Care Program 2013

Case in Point Platinum Award Best Transition of Care Program 2012

Tali Edge

Vice President at Grady Health System Atlanta

Summary

Experienced Nurse Leader with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Leadership / Management, Hospital and Nursing Operations, Care Coordination, Evidence-Based Practice, the Magnet Journey, Post-Acute and Transitions of Care, Population Health, Denials and Appeals Management, Payer relations, etc. Strong community and civic involvement.

Experience

Grady Health System
Vice President
August 2019 - Present (1 year 1 month)
Atlanta

Houston Methodist Hospital Director, Case Management and Social Work November 2016 - August 2019 (2 years 10 months) Houston, Texas

Emory Healthcare

Director of Nursing

December 2010 - December 2016 (6 years 1 month)

Coordinating and directing aspects of the rehospitalization prevention program for Emory Healthcare.

Accountable for strategic planning, program development, labor management and overall operational administration of the Transition Management program and care transitions.

Accountable for managing and overseeing Transition Management (Nurse Practitioners, Discharge Coordinators, Care Transitions Coordinators, Project Manager, etc) and Supervising MD relationships including collaborative practice agreements, TM prescriptive authority and related state regulatory and accreditation requirements.

Accountable for care coordination across the continuum to include, but not limited to, coordination of care with long term acute care hospitals, skilled nursing facilities, acute rehab facilities, etc.

Accountable for establishing policies and procedures around care coordination with home health agencies, infusion companies, etc.

Assists with leading post acute care strategy and strategic plan

Hands of Hope Nurse Practitioner July 2013 - August 2015 (2 years 2 months) Stockbridge, Georgia

To provide comprehensive and coordinated care to indigent patients. Assess, diagnose, treat, monitor, evaluate, and educate uninsured residents of Henry county Georgia.

Kindred Healthcare Resource Chief Clinical Office November 2004 - November 2010 (6 years 1 month) Atlanta, GA

Responsible for clinical operations and oversight of multiple long term acute care facilities within the East and Midwest regions. Reports included, but not limited to, Directors of Nursing, Respiratory Therapy, Radiology, Pharmacy, Education, Wound Care, Dietary/Food Services, Laboratory, Rehabilitation, Infection Control/Employee Health, Health Information Management/Medical Records, Surgical Services and Executive Assistants.

Responsible for overseeing structure, operating plans, budgets, and policies and procedures

Set appropriate staffing standards and sat on committee to enhance the patient acuity tool

Development of short and long term goals in collaboration with Chief Executive Officers, Executive Directors, Director of Quality Management and VP of Clinical Operations

Education

University of Texas at Tyler

Doctor or Nursing Practice, Nursing Administration · (2018 - 2021)

Howard University

Bachelor's of science in nursing, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse

Howard University

Master's of Science in Nursing, Family Nurse Practitioner-Board certified

University of Indianapolis - School of Business Master of Business Administration (MBA), Business Administration and Management, General